yougowords.com 2016-11-29

# Privacy Policy - You Go Words!

On every page you write information, such as poetry, you are given the option of how you want to display this information. You can choose "only me" to ensure, it is not publicly available. You can choose to not display, or to display what you write, whether it be comments (Except social network comment areas), articles, poetry or other.

Your information, is yours and yours alone. It is not sold, given away, nor provided to any third party. Your information is used solely for the purpose of You Go Words, You Go Rhymes and other personal projects you have become a part of that are a You Go Media property.

I hope you enjoy the privacy I provide on this website, and my other personal projects. If you have any concerns or questions, please ensure you contact me or leave feedback in the comment areas throughout this website.

Thank You,  
You Go Words

### My Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which You Go Words! collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the [http://www.yougowords.com](http://www.yougowords.com/) website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by You Go Words!.

**Personal identification information**

I may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit my site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources I make available on my Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit my Site anonymously. I will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

I may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with my Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to my Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How I use collected information**

You Go Words! may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _\- To improve service_  
Information you provide helps me respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * _\- To personalize user experience_  
I may use information in the aggregate to understand how my Users as a group use the services and resources provided on my Site.
  * _\- To improve my Site_  
I may use feedback you provide to improve my products and services.
  * _\- To process payments_  
I may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order.Ido not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * _\- To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature_  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics I think will be of interest to them.
  * _\- To send periodic emails_  
I may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to my mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, I include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via my Site.

**How I protect your information**

I adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on my Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. My Site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

**Sharing your personal information**

I do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. I may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with my business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on my Site that link to the sites and services of my partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. I do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from my Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to my Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on my site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to my Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Changes to this privacy policy**

You Go Words! has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When I do, I will post a notification on the main page of my Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. I encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how I am helping to protect the personal information I collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and [terms of service](http://www.yougowords.com/terms-of-service.html). If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use my Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
[You Go Words!  
http://www.yougowords.com](http://www.yougowords.com/)  
James A. Cordeiro Direct: james@yougomedia.com  
1 (77H) APP-Y444  
support@yougowords.com

This document was last updated on October 24, 2014

loading...

#### Commenting On This Word Finder.

On your downloads page area, there is information on why word downloads are not available. Please read the about page to learn who I am, and how this word finding tool works behind the scenes. This is currently a free word website, made by one dude - so to expect everything to work perfectly is terrible sense of entitlement. If you are not happy with this **free website** , I ask you to please send feedback or comment your thoughts below in a kind manner. I do want to improve the finding capabilities, and am working to do so. Your constructive and kind criticism is appreciated. You Go Words! is massive and the time it takes is tremendous. It earns money, but does not cover the expenses. Share this website with your word loving friends and comment feedback. I promise to continue to improve the finding, rhyming, poetry and filtering tools. Thank you for using You Go Words!

  * Google+
  * Page Specific

Thank you for visting. I will be adding a comments tool for all members to comment, interact and associate with the word pages!

All comments will be moderated.
